♪The way you move in slow motion♪
♪Makes me a little shy♪
♪When you say you love me♪
♪It's more than I ever imagined♪
♪Slowly♪
♪Stay by my side♪
♪Love is the warmth of everyday life♪
♪The way you move in slow motion♪
♪Makes me a little shy♪
♪You lean your forehead against mine♪
♪Then you keep grinning like a fool♪
♪Little by little♪
♪You come closer to me♪
♪A warm love song plays in my ear♪
=The One=
=Episode 23=
I showed up at just the right time.
When he grabbed your hand,
your ears were bright red.
Keep your eyes on the road.
Your younger guy's a hotshot CEO now,
and he's still crazy about you.
So what's holding you back?
I heard that these past few years,
he's been working day and night.
Through overseas markets,
his stake is almost
catching up to Ji Sinian's.
Yeah, I heard.
But
I have Tangtang. That's enough.
Of course Tangtang's adorable.
You learned to cook for her.
You quit smoking and drinking.
You're so careful now you won't
even get on a plane.
Good thing I was there when you
adopted her,
or I'd swear you gave birth to her
yourself.
She showed me what it feels like
to have someone rely on me
and trust me completely.
It's wonderful.
So,
I will never
let her grow up
without a mother.
That has nothing to do with dating.
Tangtang needs a dad.
And you need a man.
I don't.
Do you not trust men,
or are you just
afraid Cheng Lin will let you down?
Five years ago,
Tangtang came into your life
just as Cheng Lin left.
You haven't dated in five years.
Don't tell me
it's not because of Cheng Lin.
Su Yan.
Take a chance.
Did you have fun?
Yeah!
What are you doing here?
I'm here to win over
your daughter.
Tangtang.
I'm your mom's friend.
Want to be friends?
Hi, mister!
Tangtang.
Call him Mr. Cheng.
Want me to be your dad?
Cheng Lin!
So you're Cheng Lin.
You know me?
Mom says your name in her sleep.
Tangtang!
Looks like your mom
thinks about me a lot.
Check your seat belts again.
Keep Tangtang safe.
What's wrong?
Someone tampered with the brakes.
Fengqi Road is just ahead.
We'll hit the East Ring Road
in about half an hour.
Hello?
Someone tampered with our brakes.
(Fengqi Road)
Set up roadblocks on East Ring Road.
As soon as possible.
(Okay.)
(Keep your speed steady. Stay calm.)
Mom, what's wrong?
It's okay, sweetie.
Try to get some sleep.
I'll wake you up later, okay?
(Traffic police are in position.)
(Barriers ahead in five minutes.)
(Stay calm.)
Mom!
Cheng Lin!
(Su Yan.)
(Tell me.)
(What would make you feel better?)
♪Can you hear how much I miss you?♪
♪It hits like a wave I can't contain♪
♪I can't let go of the path we shared♪
♪But you said time would make it fade♪
♪Memories pile up, moment by moment♪
♪One careless word brings my walls down♪
♪I escape the past, then fall back in♪
♪Longing twists into a hopeless knot♪
♪Pulled by the past
till my world fades out♪
♪I hum this song alone♪
♪Counting every fleeting moment♪
♪Every corner still reminds me of you♪
♪Can you hear how much I miss you?♪
♪It hits like a wave I can't contain♪
♪I can't let go of the path we shared♪
♪But you said time would make it fade♪